Christmas Twister is a science fiction, drama,
action film directed by Peter Sullivan.
During the holiday season, Ethan, a meteorologist, and his wife Addison, a TV news reporter, must put aside their differences and band together to help
save others and rescue their missing children from a massive F6 twister that has unexpectedly descended upon their small Texas town.
Ethan, played by Casper Van Dien.
Addison, played by Victoria Pratt.
Logan, played by Richard Burgi.
Chloe, played by Madelyn Deutch.
Terry, played by Steven Williams.
Deb, played by Christina DeRosa.
Jami Beth Gertz ( JAY-mee; born October 28, 1965) is
an American actress and businesswoman.
Gertz had roles in the films Crossroads, Quicksilver (both 1986), Less than Zero, The Lost Boys (both 1987), and the 1980s TV series Square Pegs and
1996's Twister, as well as roles as Judy Miller in the CBS sitcom Still Standing and as Debbie Weaver in the ABC sitcom The Neighbors.
She is an owner of the Atlanta Hawks basketball team
along with her husband Tony Ressler.
The film explores themes of tornado, shopping mall,
elementary school, cell phone, mall.
The tone is intense and emotional and thought_provoking.